https://www.fireandsafetycentre.co.uk/privacy-policy.php

Data Protection and Privacy Policy
Fire and Safety Centre is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals and companies who use this web site. We employ stringent security procedures including SSL encryption, and run independently monitored daily security checks for site vulnerability through McAfee Secure to ensure our privacy and security procedures meet or exceed your expectations.
We are voluntarily registered as Data Controllers in the Information Commissioner's public register. Our Registration Number is ZA266459.
You can visit this Register at https://ico.org.uk/esdwebpages/search
The CompanyFire and Safety Centre is a trading name of Right Action Ltd.Our Registered address is 15 Atkinsons Way, Foxhills Industrial Estate. Scunthorpe, North Lincolnshire, DN15 8QJPlease read the following Privacy Policy which details how we will treat your personal data after it has been collected by us through your use of this web site.
How do we collect data?We have to collect data on you for the purposes of providing you with products and services and this will inevitably include personal data. For example we collect data:
When you purchase products or services online through the website or by telephone with our sales personnel or using any of our other distribution channels;
When you register and become an account holder;
When you enter your personal data into a sales order form on the web site;
When you speak to our customer services personnel;
When using data capture measures such as the use of cookies;
What do we do with your personal information?When you make a purchase via the site or by telephone or give any personal data as indicated above, we may need to collect information about you to process your transaction, fulfil your order and provide you with the quality of service you expect. This information may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, your address, your phone number, credit card details and email address.
Right Action Ltd is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties other than in the limited ways disclosed in this statement.
Unless we have your express consent we will only disclose personal data to third parties when required for the purpose of completing your transaction with us. This is subject to the proviso that we may disclose your data to certain permitted third parties, such as within our own Group, our professional advisers who are bound by confidentiality codes, our website hosts and developers and when we are legally obliged to disclose your data.
We request personal and sensitive information from customers on our sales order form. Certain essential information must be provided (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date) as this information is used for billing purposes and to fulfil your order. If we have trouble processing an order, your contact information is also used to get in touch to resolve any problems.
CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information whilst you are on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. By setting a cookie on our site, we can recognise returning customers and registered customers and account holders which can save time when completing order details. You can block cookies but they are required for certain parts of the site to work correctly and will enhance your experience when using and revisiting our web site. For more information on cookies and the way they are used on this web site, please visit https://www.fireandsafetycentre.co.uk/cookies.php.
SharingWe use a secure credit card processing company to collect payments for goods and services purchased online. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes and operate SSL software security to protect your data.
LinksThis web site contains links to other sites we consider relevant to our customers. Please be aware that Fire and Safety Centre is not responsible for the privacy practices of these and any other sites. We encourage our users to be vigilant when they leave our site, to read the privacy statements of any web site that collects your personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Right Action Ltd.
SecurityThis website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), the information is encrypted and is protected by SSL, the best encryption software in the industry. The security of our site from external attacks by hackers is independently monitored and verified by McAfee Secure on a daily basis.
While SSL encryption is used to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect your information off-line. All information collected, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted within our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific task (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
Correction/Updating Personal Information:If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your post code), or if you no longer desire our services, we provide a way to correct, update or remove your personal data stored by us. This can be done by contacting our Customer Support in the first instance.
Choice/Opt-outIf you use this site to purchase goods or services you may occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers, and a newsletter. However, out of respect for the privacy of our users we will only send this information to you if you choose to "opt in" to this correspondence. This can be done at the point of placing an order on our website or through our newsletter "opt in" page, which can be found here.
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may also opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at sales@fireandsafetycentre.co.uk
ConsentBy disclosing your personal information to us when using this web site or over the telephone, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by Right Action Ltd in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.
Notification of ChangesIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we need to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will only use information in accordance with the privacy policy in force at the time the information was collected.
0  Item(s)£0.00  ex VAT£0.00  inc VAT
Trustpilot
Testimonials
Read more.
Fire Extinguishers Extinguisher Spares and clearance stock Extinguisher AccessoriesFire Extinguisher Cabinets and StandsExtinguisher ConsumablesFire BlanketsHose ReelsFire BucketsFire Alarms & DetectorsEscape LaddersFirst Aid KidsFireproof StorageOther Safety ProductsBrigade EquipmentFire Safety Signs and NoticesFire Extinguisher MaintenanceFire Extinguisher Advice
Trustpilot
Atkinsons Way, Foxhills Industrial Estate, Scunthorpe, North Lincolnshire DN15 8QJ
© 2020 Fire and Safety Centre, all rights reserved.
